/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data10_3', {
    title: '10.3 Adding Mixed Numbers',
    path: '10.3-adding-mixed-numbers',
    children: [{
        title: 'Adding Mixed Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\xA0',
                answer: '\\css{\\rowgrp{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0  \xA0 \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{5}}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{4}}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 \xA0 \xA0 \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{31}}{\\input{20}}}}}{centerTableText4}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}',
                answer: '\\css{\\rowgrp{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0  \xA0 \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{5}}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{4}}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 \xA0 \xA0 \xA0}}{\\input{20}}}}{centerTableText4}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }',
                answer: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 \xA0 \xA0 }}{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{5}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0 \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{16}}{\\str{20}}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0 \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{15}}{\\str{20}}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\str{Add the fractions:}',
                answer: '\\css{\\rowgrp{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0  \xA0 \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{16}}{\\str{20}}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{15}}{\\str{20}}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 \xA0 \xA0 \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{31}}{\\input{20}}}}}{centerTableText4}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Mixed Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{2}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{5}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{9}}{\\input{10}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{2}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{5}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{10}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{2}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{5}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{15}}{\\fracstr{10}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{6}}{\\fracstr{10}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Subtract the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{15}}{\\fracstr{10}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{6}}{\\fracstr{10}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{9}}{\\input{10}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Mixed Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{6}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{8}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{17}}{\\input{24}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{6}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{8}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{24}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{6}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{8}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{20}}{\\fracstr{24}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{3}}{\\fracstr{24}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Subtract the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{20}}{\\fracstr{24}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{24}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{17}}{\\input{24}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Mixed Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{8}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{2}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{1}}{\\input{8}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{8}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{2}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{8}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{8}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{2}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\fracstr{8}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{4}}{\\fracstr{8}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Subtract the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{8}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{4}}{\\fracstr{8}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{1}}{\\input{8}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Mixed Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{7}}{\\str{16}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{8}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\input{16}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{7}}{\\fracstr{16}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{8}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{16}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{7}}{\\fracstr{16}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{8}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{7}}{\\fracstr{16}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{2}}{\\fracstr{16}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Subtract the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{7}}{\\fracstr{16}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{16}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\input{16}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Mixed Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{22}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{49}}{\\input{44}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{4}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{22}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{44}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{4}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{22}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{55}}{\\fracstr{44}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{6}}{\\fracstr{44}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Subtract the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{55}}{\\fracstr{44}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{6}}{\\fracstr{44}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{49}}{\\input{44}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Mixed Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{11}}{\\str{8}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{6}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{13}}{\\input{24}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{11}}{\\fracstr{8}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{6}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{24}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{11}}{\\fracstr{8}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{6}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{33}}{\\fracstr{24}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{20}}{\\fracstr{24}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Subtract the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{33}}{\\fracstr{24}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{20}}{\\fracstr{24}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{13}}{\\input{24}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Mixed Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{11}}{\\str{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{3}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{6}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\input{12}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{11}}{\\fracstr{12}}}{\\row{\\str{, \xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{3}}}{\\row{\\str{,\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{6}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{12}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{11}}{\\str{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{3}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{6}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{11}}{\\fracstr{12}}}{\\str{, \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{4}}{\\fracstr{12}}}{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{2}}{\\fracstr{12}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Subtract the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{11}}{\\str{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\input{12}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Mixed Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{13}}{\\str{10}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{5}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{9}}{\\input{20}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{13}}{\\fracstr{10}}}{\\row{\\str{, \xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{4}}}{\\row{\\str{,\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{5}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{20}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{13}}{\\str{10}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{5}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{26}}{\\fracstr{20}}}{\\str{, \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\fracstr{20}}}{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{12}}{\\fracstr{20}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Subtract the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{26}}{\\str{20}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{20}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{12}}{\\str{20}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{9}}{\\input{20}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Mixed Numbers',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{7}}{\\str{3}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{5}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{53}}{\\input{60}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{7}}{\\fracstr{3}}}{\\row{\\str{, \xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{4}}}{\\row{\\str{,\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{5}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{60}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{7}}{\\str{3}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{5}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{140}}{\\fracstr{60}}}{\\str{, \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{75}}{\\fracstr{60}}}{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{12}}{\\fracstr{60}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Subtract the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{140}}{\\str{60}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{75}}{\\str{60}}}{\\sign{\xA0 - \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{12}}{\\str{60}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{53}}{\\input{60}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }]
});
